Art and Architecture of Japan Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Japan 19th and 20th century Collection (Box 17)
  - Sculpture (Box 19)
    - Various Artists (Box 19)
    - Arakawa Shusaku, 1936- (Box 19)
    - Asahi Gyokuzan, 1843-1923 (Box 19)
    - Asakura Fumio, 1883-1964 (Box 19)
    - Brandon, Reiko Mochinaga, 1935- (Box 19)
    - Endo Toshikatsu, 1950- (Box 19)
    - Fujikawa Yuzo, 1883-1935 (Box 19)
    - Fujita Bunzo, 1861-1934 (Box 19)
    - Hashimoto Heihachi, 1887-1935 (Box 19)
    - Hiragushi Denchu, 1872-1979 (Box 19)
    - Kawamata, Tadashi, 1953- (Box 19)
    - Kubota, Shigeko (Box 19)
    - Kudo Tetsumi, 1935-1990 (Box 19)
    - Kusama Yayoi, 1929- (Box 19)
      - Before 1960 (Box 19)
      - 1960-1964 (Box 19)
      - 1965-1967 (Box 19)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 19)
      - 1980's (Box 19)
    - Lee, U Fan, 1936- [Slide box 113] (Box 19)
    - Mori, Mariko, 1967- (Box 19)
    - Naganuma Moriyoshi (Shukei), 1857-1942 (Box 19)
    - Nakakara Teijiro, 1881-1921 (Box 19)
    - Noguchi Isamu, 1904-1988 (Box 19)
    - Numata Kazumasa (Ichiga), 1873-1954 (Box 19)
    - Ogiwara Morie, 1879-1910 (Box 19)
    - Okuma Ujihiro, 1856-1934 (Box 19)
    - Ono, Yoko, 1933- (Box 19)
    - Sawada Seiko, b. 1894 (Box 19)
    - Shinkai Taketaro, 1868-1927 (Box 19)
    - Shirai Uzan, 1864-1928 (Box 19)
    - Suga Kishio, 1944- (Box 19)
    - Takamura Kotaro, 1883-1956 (Box 19)
    - Takamura Koun, 1852-1934 (Box 19)
    - Tatehata Taimu, 1880-1942 (Box 19)
    - Tobari Kogan, 1882-1927 (Box 19)
    - Tokushige, Emiko, 1939- (Box 19)
    - Toya, Shigeo, 1947- (Box 19)
    - Yagi Kazuo, 1918-1979 (Box 19)
    - Yoshimura Masunobu, 1932- (Box 19)